<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Brave the Future</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="motorsports">UOIT Motorsports was founded by a group of forward thinking individuals at the University of Ontario Institute of Technology in 2017. We are dedicated to researching and developing the future of automotive propulsion technologies, with the backing of our faculty and sponsors. We place value and emphasis on teamwork and efficiency as well as the art of knowledge transfer here at UOIT Motorsports.</string>
    <string name="uoit_motorsports">UOIT Motorsports</string>
    <string name="ri3d">Robot in 3 Days (RI3D) is a program meant to first but not foremost entertain and secondly, to inspire and spark ideas. RI3D is a great way to start teams o during the first week of Robot Build Season. Particularly for low resource teams, RI3D allows them to consider di erent prototypes that they would otherwise not have been able to build. RI3D is a great resource for many teams. Many of the members on our team have benefited greatly from learning what other RI3D have had to o er in previous years.</string>
    <string name="usuelections">UOIT Student Union exists to enhance our student experience. The union is governed by student representatives elected by their peers each year. These students work together to lead the union’s initiatives. It’s your union, your voice. Make the most of your university experience. Run for the office, attend the forum and cast your vote online.</string>
    <string name="gears">GEARS is an organized community inside our campus residences for Engineering students to live surrounded by their Engineering peers. The GEARS community hosts study sessions, provides peer support, and leads to lasting friendships.</string>
    <string name="ignite">Ignite is the university\'s largest orientation specifically geared toward students who are beginning classes in September. Fall Orientation activities provide fun and exciting opportunities for all incoming students in the university\'s diverse student population. Ignite is a not only a great way to make new friends prior to starting classes, but it also allows students the opportunity to explore campus and learn about the university\'s vibrant campus culture.</string>
    <string name="transferdc">Our unique college-to-university programs provide numerous opportunities to apply the credits you earned at college toward a university degree, expanding your career options when you graduate. Some programs offer direct entry and others require completion of specific bridge courses.</string>
    <string name="drt">The Universal Transit Pass (U-Pass) provides eligible students at participating colleges and universities unlimited travel on DRT and OneFare DRT-GO Transit routes. Perfect for commuting convenience for off-campus students.</string>
    <string name="soce">Societies are student-run groups that represent a particular area of study. Students MUST submit a complete nomination package during the nomination period (Feb 25-Mar 1) to qualify for candidacy. Download the package during the nomination period and submit it in-person at the Club and Society Office or the Downtown Union Cafe. Nomination Packages coming soon (Feb 25)</string>
    <string name="btf">Brave The Future is an ambitious campaign to develop the space and opportunities necessary to create transformational change, to reimagine higher learning through the lens of technology, and to deliver an educational experience that meets students in the world where they live today, and prepares them for the world they will create tomorrow.</string>
    <string name="pass">Weekly review sessions that are available to students in challenging courses. Sessions are informal, fun and interactive! They are designed to help students succeed by improving understanding of course material, developing study strategies, and preparing for tests and exams.</string>
    <string name="sami">a mental health initiative which focuses on furthering a student assistance network for students who may be suffering from mental health problems. With the help of the Ontario Society of Professional Engineers (OSPE), EngSoc is providing Free Mental Health First Aid training sessions for Engineering Students.</string>
    <string name="mental">Everybody can benefit from counselling. It can help you appreciate and reach your personal potential to fully benefit from your university experience. We also help students with a variety of mental health difficulties often prompted by usual developmental and life concerns.</string>
    <string name="tele">Since opening its doors in 2003, the university has provided industry-leading hardware and software tools across the curriculum to produce tech-savvy graduates who are adaptable to technological change. The Technology-Enriched Learning Environment (TELE) program provides students with tools to aid in academic success through provided laptops or Bring Your Own Device (BYOD).</string>
    <string name="labs">We offer a number of world-class research laboratories with infrastructure dedicated to conducting a unique blend of undergraduate and graduate research in a variety of research areas. Our students are committed to research that can be translated to reality and continue to demonstrate this commitment through their research outcomes.</string>
    <string name="usu">University of Ontario Institute of Technology Student Union (UOIT SU) exists to enhance the student experience. We are an advanced learning organization which encourages equality and equity, while providing essential services for the students of UOIT.</string>
</resources>
